{
    "q1": {
        "question": "For \\( f(x) \\), what does the transformation \\( -f(x)\\) do?",
        "answer": "Reflect \\( f(x) \\) over the \\( x \\) axis",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "Reflect \\( f(x) \\) over the \\( y \\) axis",
            "Make all \\( y \\) values negative",
            "Reflect \\( f(x) \\) over the \\( x \\) axis",
            "Make all \\( x \\) values negative"
        ]
    },
    "q2": {
        "question": "For \\( f(x) \\), what does the transformation \\( f(-x) \\) do?",
        "answer": "Reflect \\( f(x) \\) over the \\( y \\) axis",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "Reflect \\( f(x) \\) over the \\( y \\) axis",
            "Make all \\( x \\) values negative",
            "Reflect \\( f(x) \\) over the \\( x \\) axis",
            "Make all \\( y \\) values negative"
        ]
    },
    "q3": {
        "question": "For a circular graph with equation \\( (x-5)^2 + (y-10)^2 = 25 \\), where is the centre?",
        "answer": "\\( (5, 10) \\)",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "\\( (10, 5) \\)",
            "\\( (5, 10) \\)",
            "\\( (-5, -10) \\)",
            "\\( (-10, -5) \\)"
        ]
    },
    "q4": {
        "question": "For a circular graph with equation \\( (x-5)^2 + (y-10)^2 = 25 \\), what is the length of the radius?",
        "answer": "5",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "\\( 25 \\)",
            "\\( 50 \\)",
            "\\( 25^2 \\)",
            "\\( \\sqrt[2]{25} \\)"
        ]
    },
    "q5": {
        "question": "Which is true for \\( f(x) = \\frac{1}{x^2} \\) ?",
        "answer": "\\( f(x) > 0 \\) for all \\( x \\)",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "\\( f(x) < 0 \\) for all \\( x \\)",
            "\\( f(x) > 0 \\) for all \\( x \\)",
            "\\( f(x) \\) travels through the origin \\( (0, 0) \\)",
            "\\( f(x) \\) is a quadratic curve"
        ]
    },
    "q6": {
        "question": "For \\( f(x) \\), what does the transformation \\( f(x + 2) \\) do?",
        "answer": "Shift \\( f(x) \\) in \\( x \\) by \\( -2 \\)",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "Shift \\( f(x) \\) in \\( x \\) by \\( -2 \\)",
            "Shift \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( -2 \\)",
            "Shift \\( f(x) \\) in \\( x \\) by \\( +2 \\)",
            "Stretch \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( \\times 2 \\)"
        ]
    },
    "q7": {
        "question": "For \\( f(x) \\), what does the transformation \\( f(x) + 10 \\) do?",
        "answer": "Shift \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( +10 \\)",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "Shift \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( +10 \\)",
            "Alters the gradient of  \\( f(x) \\)",
            "Stretch \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( \\frac{1}{10} \\)",
            "Shift \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( -10 \\)"
        ]
    },
    "q8": {
        "question": "For \\( f(x) \\), what does the transformation \\( f(2x) \\) do?",
        "answer": "Stretch \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( \\frac{1}{2} \\)",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "Stretch \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( \\frac{1}{2} \\)",
            "Stretch \\( f(x) \\) in \\( x \\) by \\( \\frac{1}{2} \\)",
            "Stretch \\( f(x) \\) in \\( x \\) by \\( 2 \\)",
            "Stretch \\( f(x) \\) in \\( y \\) by \\( 2 \\)"
        ]
    },
    "q9": {
        "question": "Which is true for \\( f(x) = \\frac{1}{x} \\) ?",
        "answer": "",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "When \\( x \\) is positive, \\( y \\) is negative",
            "When \\( x \\) is negative, \\( y \\) is positive",
            "\\( \\frac{1}{x} \\) is undefined when \\( x = 0 \\)",
            "for f(x) = \\( \\frac{1}{x} \\), \\( y \\) is always positive"
        ]
    },
    "q10": {
        "question": "Which is true?",
        "answer": "A cubic graph starts from \\( - \\infty \\) and rises to \\( + \\infty \\)",
        "hint": "",
        "options": [
            "A positive cubic graph starts from \\( - \\infty \\) and rises to \\( + \\infty \\)",
            "A positive quadratic graph starts from \\( - \\infty \\) and rises to \\( + \\infty \\)",
            "A positive quartic graph starts from \\( - \\infty \\) and returns to \\( - \\infty \\)",
            "A negative quadratic graph starts from \\( + \\infty \\) and returns to \\( + \\infty \\)"
        ]
    }
}